Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1935-2002.
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-2002.
- Series V. National and international activities and interests
  - China
    - Sub-subseries: Specialists and project staff
      - C. Rikert - Fudan, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 67)
      - W.E. Spicer (Box 30, Folder 68)
      - Phipps/Fudan (Box 30, Folder 69)
      - W. Kohn (Box 30, Folder 70)
      - Charles Kittel (Box 30, Folder 71)
      - A.N. Bohr (Box 30, Folder 72)
      - M.A. Breuer (Box 30, Folder 73)
      - R.K. Brayton - Fudan (Box 30, Folder 74)
      - K. Shimoda, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 75)
      - Derek Shaw (Box 30, Folder 76)
      - S.D. Smith (Box 30, Folder 77)
      - F.H. Eisen/Beijing Normal, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 78)
      - S. Kwok/Beijing Normal, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 79)
      - J.B. Oke/Beijing Normal, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 80)
      - Dr. Remy Lemaire, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 81)
      - S.K. Mitra, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 82)
      - Y.T. Feng, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 83)
      - Zhang Jian to H. Beemer; Y. Uemura; DRC to Zhang Guangdou; Chin. Engr. (Box 30, Folder 84)
      - DRC to Zhang Jian; DRC to Proposed Members, June 17, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 85)
      - Lionel Salem, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 86)
      - O.C. Zienkiewicz Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 87)
      - Suggested Initial Contact Letter, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 88)
      - Project Specialist Statement (Box 30, Folder 89)
      - Selection of Foreign Specialists, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 90)
      - Specialists, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 91-92)
      - Specialist List, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 93)
      - Toshibaru, Tako, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 94)
      - List of Specialists to be Invited, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 95)
      - Specialists, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 96)
      - John K. Tien (Box 30, Folder 97)
      - Wen H. Ko, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 98)
      - Specialists, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 99)
      - NCR Group Recognition Award, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 100)
      - Lionel Salem, 1988-1990 (Box 30, Folder 101)
    - Sub-subseries: Reports
      - Staff Appraisal Report - University Development Project, June 1, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 102)
      - Socialist Economic Development World Bank Report (Box 30, Folder 103)
      - Staff Appraisal Report UDP (Box 30, Folder 104)
      - CUDP Progress Report, Oct. 30, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 105)
      - Corson Report, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 30, Folder 106)
      - Pestel Report, Nov. 1982 (Box 30, Folder 107)
      - O. Zienkiewicz Report, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 30, Folder 108)
      - Salem Report, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 30, Folder 109)
      - H. Zienkiewicz Report, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 30, Folder 110)
      - D.F. Finn Report, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 30, Folder 111)
      - Trip Report, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 30, Folder 112)
      - E.C. Slater Report, Apr. 1983 (Box 30, Folder 113)
      - Distinguished Scholars Exchange Program; China Trip Report by Lieng-Huang Lee, May 1983 (Box 30, Folder 114)
      - Tako Trip Report, Aug.-Sept. 17, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 115)
      - CUDP I - Staff Appraisal Report, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 116)
      - Donald P. Greenberg - Report on Visit to Tsinghau University, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 117)
      - Lionel Salem Report, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 118)
      - E. Leonard Jossem, Report on Visit to Beijing Normal University, Oct. 1989 (Box 30, Folder 119)
      - CUDP I and II - Reports, 1986-1991 (Box 30, Folder 120)
    - Sub-subseries: Individual universities
      - Beijing Agricultural University (Box 30, Folder 121)
      - Beijing Agricultural University, Apr. 18, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 122)
      - Beijing Medical College (Box 30, Folder 123)
      - DRC Assessment of Beijing Normal University, May 12, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 124)
      - Beijing Normal University Calling Cards (Box 30, Folder 125)
      - Beijing University, Apr. 19, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 126)
      - Chongqing University, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 127)
      - Dalien Institute of Technology - A.B. Templeman, Consultant, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 128)
      - Yi-Yuan Yu, Dalian Institute of Technology (Box 30, Folder 129)
      - W.T. Lippincott, East China Normal University, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 130)
      - East China University of Chemical Technology (Box 30, Folder 131)
      - Fudan University, Fall, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 132)
      - Fudan University - Course Syllabi (Box 30, Folder 133)
      - Fudan University (Box 30, Folder 134)
      - Fudan University - Computer Center (Box 30, Folder 135)
      - Fudan University - Semiconductor Physics (Box 30, Folder 136)
      - Peter Y. Yu, Fudan University, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 137)
      - Yo-Yat Cheung, Fudan University, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Huazhong (Central China) University, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Feasibility Study for the Establishment of the Chemical Engineering Department in Hauzhong University, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Booklet - Institute of Acoustics-Academic Sinica, Beijing, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Nanjing University, UDP (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Nanjing Visit, Apr. 24-27, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Nankar University DRC, Apr. 20, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Peking Medical College, DRC, Apr. 18, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Nankai University (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Peking University (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Peking University Agenda, Nov. 25, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Qinghua Visit, Apr.-May 4, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Civil Construction Lab, Qinghua, DRC, Apr. 18, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Thermal Engineering Lab, Qinghua, DRC, Apr .18, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Hydraulics and Fluid Mechanics Lab, Qinghua, DRC, Apr .18, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Optics Lab in the Department of Precision Instruments, Qinghua, DRC, Apr .18, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Qinghua Computer Center DRC, Apr .18, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 17-18)
      - Qinghua Computer Science Program DRC, Apr .18, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - World Bank Loan Status at Qinghua University, DRC, Apr .18, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Wen-Jei Yang, Qinghua University (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Sichuan University (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Tianjin (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Tianjin University DRC, May 10, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - Tsinghua University (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Wuhan University (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - Wuhan University Agenda, Nov. 15-17, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - Xian Jiaotong University (Box 31, Folder 28-33)
      - Duncan T. Moore, Zhejiang University, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Sub-subseries: Conference papers
      - "Address to the Second Work Conference on Open Research Laboratories in the Chinese Academy of Sciences," by Zhou Guangzhao (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - "…Antibiotics and Traditional Chinese Medicine," Zhang S-G and Hu Y-C (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - "Biotechnology and the Office of Technology Assessment," G.S. Kolsrud (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - "Characteristics of University of Science and Technology of China," Ren Z-S and Si Y-H (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - "China Addresses Critical Issues of Science, Technology, and Economic Development," P.M. Perrolle NSF (Box 31, Folder 39)
      - "China's Programs for Science and Technological Development," Luo Wei (Box 31, Folder 40)
      - "Education and Development of S and T Personnel" Hu Ping (Box 31, Folder 41)
      - "Financial Management in US Higher Education," D.F. Finn (Box 31, Folder 42)
      - "General Issues Related to R and D in Industry," R.A. Chairpie (Box 31, Folder 43)
      - "Historical Precedents for Our New Relations with China", May 24, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 44)
      - "Meaning and Context of Science Policy in China and US-Comparison," R.P. Suttmeier (Box 31, Folder 45)
      - "Policies of Industrial R and D in the Period of Adjustment," Yu D., Cao T., Xu S. (Box 31, Folder 46)
      - "Policies of US towards Industrial Innovation," R.R. Nelson (Box 31, Folder 47)
      - "Notes toward a Theory Transfer," R.A. Frosch (Box 31, Folder 48)
      - "Research and Development Management: Transfer of Technology," G.P. Dineen (Box 31, Folder 49)
      - Research Development and Economic Benefit of the Shanghai Industry," Xia Yulong Gu (Box 31, Folder 50)
      - "Resolution of China's Rural Energy Requirements," Wu W. and Chen E-J (Box 31, Folder 51)
      - "Science Policy Study Group Report: Issues and Observations," L.A. Orleans (Box 31, Folder 52)
      - Science, Society, Economy Papers by J.H. Gibbons, T.Bull, and T.H. Ratchford (Box 31, Folder 53)
      - "Scientific and Technological Policy of Enviornemntal Protection," Peng Guo (Box 31, Folder 54)
      - "Synthesis of Insulin and Yeast Alanine tRNA," Hu Y-C, Chen C-Q, Jiang C-C, Luo D, Huang A-Z (Box 31, Folder 55)
      - "Technological Change and Economic Growth," E. Mansfield (Box 31, Folder 56)
      - "Technological Development Strategy of Agriculture in China," Xi H. and Wu M. (Box 31, Folder 57)
      - "Technology Assessment and Environmental Impact Assessment," H. Brooks (Box 31, Folder 58)
      - "Training and Utilization of Scientists and Engineers in U.S.," C.P. Ailes and F. Rushing (Box 31, Folder 59)
      - "Utilization and Transformation of the North China Plan," Huang B. and Jiana D. (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - Sub-subseries: Chinese students and scholars abroad CU/China relations
      - Taipei Trip, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 61)
      - Taiwan and Hong Kong Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 31, Folder 62)
      - Names of Chinese Visitors, May 21, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 63)
      - Taiwan Trip Report - Jerry D. Wilcox, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 64)
      - Cao Guisheng, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 65)
      - People to Study Abroad (Box 31, Folder 66)
      - Thor Rhodin, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 67)
      - Thor Rhodin, June 1984 (Box 31, Folder 68)
      - Statler, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 69)
      - Chen Visit, July 1984 (Box 31, Folder 70)
      - Chen Te-Ming (Box 31, Folder 71)
      - Cornellians in China, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 72)
      - CU/China Trip, June 1984 (Box 31, Folder 73)
      - Dinner with Chinese Ambassador, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 74)
      - Zhou Wen Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 75)
      - Zhang Mei-Yi Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 76)
      - Wei Mu Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 77)
      - Ma, Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 78)
      - Wu Wei (Box 31, Folder 79)
      - Chen Ching-Chiang (Box 31, Folder 80)
      - Cornell/China Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 81)
      - Misc. Correspondence, Chinese Applying to Cornell (Box 31, Folder 82)
      - AAAS Symposium on Technology Transfer in China, May 1986 (Box 31, Folder 83)
      - Request From Zhang Guangdou, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 84)
      - Students Abroad (Box 31, Folder 85)
      - Cornell-China Fellowship, 1990's (Box 31, Folder 86)
      - Conference Reassessing UC-China Ties, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 87)
  - Government-University-Industry Research Roundtable
    - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 88)
    - Demp Project (Box 31, Folder 89)
    - Science and Technology Committee (Box 31, Folder 90)
    - Corson Chrome File I (Box 31, Folder 91)
    - Corson Chrome File II (Box 31, Folder 92)
    - University/Industry/Government Collaboration on Research in Parallel Computing, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 93)
    - Revitalizing Truman's Science Legacy, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 94)
    - Roundtable Personnel - Misc., 1983 (Box 31, Folder 95)
    - Roundtable Council Members, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 96)
    - Roundtable, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 97)
    - Letter to F. Press, Apr. 27, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 98)
    - Roundtable Funding, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 99)
    - Lynn Thomas Correspondence, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Roundtable Misc. Correspondence, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - National Academy of Science Symposium, Oct. 1, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 39th National Conference on the Advancement of Research, Sept. 29-Oct. 2, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - GUIRR Misc. Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 5-7)
    - GUIRR (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Roundtable, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - GUIRR, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Don Phillips, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Forum Exec. Director (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - WG I (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - WG II (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - "Multidisciplinary Research and Education," Draft, GUIRR Working Group II, Feb. 26, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Roundtable, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Visegrad, Hungarg Conference, May 2-5, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Working Groups on Academic Research Enterprise, June 26-27, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Working Groups on Academic Research Enterprise, Oct. 17, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Council On Scientific Meetings, Budapest, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Council On Scientific Meetings, Budapest, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Roundtable Council Meeting, Nov. 29-30, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Council Meeting, July 9-10, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 23-24)
    - Council Meeting, Mar. 12-13, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Council Meeting, Mar. 12-13, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Council Meeting, Oct. 8-9, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Working Group, July 6-7, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 28-29)
    - Working Group, Aug. 25, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Working Group, Sept. 19-20, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 31-32)
    - Working Group, Nov. 1-2, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Working Group, Feb. 1-2, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 34-35)
    - Working Group, May 16-17, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 36-37)
    - Council Meeting, June 25-26, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - Working Group - Briefing Book, Jan. 10, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Working Group - The Sciences and Technology within the Academic Enterprise: Status, Trends, and Issues: Part One, Draft, Apr. 24, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Miscellany: Council Retreat; Academic Facility Funding - Scanley Draft; Prospectus prepared by SRI International; MIT - Growing Business for the Future, 1995; 1987 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Working Group - Fateful Choices: The Future of the US Academic Research Enterprise, Draft, Oct. 14, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Future National Research Policies within the Industrialized Nations - A Symposium and Symposium Participants; also, Science and Technology in the Academic Enterprise - A Discussion Paper (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - National Security Controls and University Research (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Towards a Partnership: Higher Education-Government-Industry; Fateful Choices: The Future of the US Academic Research Enterprise (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Academic Expenditures for Science and Engineering: Past, Present, Future - Working Draft; University Research in an Era of Institutional and Technological Change, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Academy activities
    - Sub-subseries: Scientific Communication and National Security ("Corson Report")
      - Buisness Week Clip, Mar. 29, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - C & EN Articles, Apr. 5, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Chem. And Eng. News Clip, Feb. 22, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Clearance (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - DRC - Defense Dept. Clearance (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Committee Membership (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - W. Donald Cooke Drafts (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Cooke Paper and Memo, "Restrictions on Accad. Res. And Nat'l Interest" (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Coop. And Sharing among Microelectronic Research Centers, Robert L. Sproul, Apr. 7, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - DRC Panel Appt. (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Designation of Ratchford as AAAS Liaison (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - D.O.D. Censorship of Papers (Box 33, Folder 28)
      - Draft II and III; Corson Presentation to Panel (Box 33, Folder 29)
      - Funding for Panel (Box 33, Folder 30)
      - "The Government-University-Science Forum," J. Sardner (drafts), June 14, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - House of Reps, Comm. of Science and Technology Impact of National Security, Mar. 29, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 32)
      - IEEE Position Paper (Box 33, Folder 33)
      - Industry Responses (Box 33, Folder 34)
      - Initial Papers (Box 33, Folder 35)
      - "Leakage of US Technology…"; "CIA Tallies Technology…", May 6, May 3, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 36)
      - "Limitations on Science Communications and Universities," J.D. Roberts (drafts), June 25, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 37)
      - Meeting with Mr. Waring, D.O.D., 1982 (Box 33, Folder 38)
      - NAS Meeting, July 1-19, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 39)
      - NAS Meeting, June 14, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 40)
      - Membership: AAAS Committee on Scientific Freedom and Responsibility (Box 33, Folder 41)
      - Military Electronics/ Countermeasures, Interview with B. Inman, Jan. 1983 (Box 33, Folder 42)
      - The MIT Interim Report on the Changing Nature of Information Draft, Apr. 2, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 43)
      - NAS Press Release, Mar. 26, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 44)
      - National Security Information (Box 33, Folder 45)
      - Dorathy Nelkin (Box 33, Folder 46)
      - Newsweek: "A Surge of Foreign Students:" "Spies in the Classroom", May 17, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 47)
      - Notes, Mar. 29-30, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 48)
      - Overview of the Export Admin. Program, Oct. 1981 (Box 33, Folder 49)
      - NAS Panel - End (Box 33, Folder 50)
      - Panel Meetings (Box 33, Folder 51)
      - Panel Meeting, June 8, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 52)
      - Panel Meeting, May 27-28, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 53)
      - Panel Meeting, May 27-28, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 54)
      - Panel Meeting (continued), May 1982 (Box 33, Folder 55)
      - Panel Meeting, Apr. 16-17, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 56)
      - Panel Meeting: Minutes, Apr. 16-17, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 57)
      - Panel Meeting, Mar. 1982 (Box 33, Folder 58)
      - Panel Misc. Correspondence (Indirect) (Box 33, Folder 59)
      - Panel Misc. Memos (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Panel on Scientific Communication and National Security (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Panel on Scientific Communication and National Security - Draft Report, Sept. 7, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Panel on Scientific Communication and National Security, Sept. 7, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Panel on Scientific Communication - General (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - R&D Management Digest, Apr. 1982 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - "The Radiowave Syndrome," by Michael Gold (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Resume: Dr. L.E. McCray (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - "Role and Responsibility of Defense," By Michael Lorenzo, May 11, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Washington Post: "Science and the CIA", Apr. 8, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Scientific Communication, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 11-12)
      - Scientific Communication (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - "Selling the Russians the Rope," Thane Gustafson, Apr. 1981 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - H. Shapiro Draft, July 19, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - "Soviet Acquisition of Western Technology", Apr. 1982 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - "The Soviet Connection I," by Richard N. Perle (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Statement to Committee on Science and Technology Subcommittees, May 24, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Stratton Report (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Study by the Panel (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Tech. Trans. DRC Bio Info. (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Tech. Trans. - Invitations Responses (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Tech. Trans. - Misc. Correspondence (Direct) (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Tech. Trans. at Issue: The Academic Viewpoint (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - "Think Piece" (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - "US Computer Export Control Policies: Value Conflicts and Policy Choices," S.E. Goodman, Apr. 14, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - Draft: US Participation (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Weinberger: "The Technology Security Program", 1986 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Woods Hale Assignments, Meeting Minutes, May-June 1987 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - York Report (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Articles on Report (Box 34, Folder 31-32)
      - Physics Today (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - Responses to Report (Box 34, Folder 34-35)
      - Panel: Misc. Papers (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - Misc. Background (Box 34, Folder 37-38)
      - Relevant Papers (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - Scientific Freedom and National Security (Box 34, Folder 40-42)
    - Other academy files
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Fellowship certificate, May 14, 1969 (Mapcase-folder 1)
      - Fellows of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Dinner in Rochester, Apr. 4, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - NAE Annual Meeting, Oct. 1989 (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - NRC Certificate and Snapshot (Box 34, Folder 46)
      - Commission on Natural Resource Editorial Services (Box 34, Folder 47)
      - NAE Correspondence re Bueche Award, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 48)
      - Arthur M. Bueche Award, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 50)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 5-6)
      - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1980's-1990's (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Education Advisory Board (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Election, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Electoral Information, Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Financial Com., 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Fostering Flexibility in the Engineering Work Force (DRC Committee Chairman) (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Memberships, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - International S&T Workshop, Sept. 28-29, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - New Reports (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Public Welfare Medal (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Permafrost Conference, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - NRC S&T Workshop, Sept. 28-29, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Electronic Power from Orbit - Report, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Electronic Power from Orbit - Report continued, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Defense Science Board
    - Defense Science Board Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 24-27)
    - Defense Science Board Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 28-31)
    - Defense Science Board Meeting, Boston, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Engineers Joint Council
    - Engineers Joint Council (Box 35, Folder 33-40)
  - Panel on the Future of Government in NY
    - Panel on the Future of Government in NY, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 41-43)
  - Japan-related activities
    - Tsukuba Research Consolation, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Science and Technology - To Advance National Goals: Science Policies in the US and Japan, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Agreement between US and Japan on Cooperation in Research and Development in Science and Technology, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - US-Japan Science Policy Seminar, Honolulu, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - National Science Foundation - US-Japan Science Policy Seminar, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - 15th Cochairman's Meeting of US-Japan Committee on Scientific Cooperation, Invitation and Meeting List, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Tokyo Meeting - Correspondence; Policy Study Group, 1992; 1990 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Survey of Research - Development in Japan; Overview of Nine Research Institutes in Japan; Japan's Life Sciences, 1994; 1992 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - US-Japan Policy Seminar, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Japan's Basic Law for Science and Technology, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - US-Japan High Tech Policy Study Group, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 11-14)
  - Other national activities and interests